

Carrye Gaulin

(910) 336-7845 carryegaulin033178@gm ail.com

Lewiston, ME 04240

SUMMARY

Experienced Bartender with 15+ years of experience in field. Strong ability to improve team performance and grow bar sales through exceptional customer service and leadership skills. Returning to my passion of computer science and ready to shift gears and learn everything I can to add value to a company I can stand behind. With my combined skills of customer service, problem solving on the fly and my new found technical skills and deep desire to continue learning I believe I will be an asset to the right team.

SKILLS

- Outstanding customer service
- Marketing and sales experience
- Outgoing personality
- SQL
- MySQL

- Databases
- JavaScript
- HTML5
- Mocha
- React

EXPERIENCE

Bartender

Islamorada, FL

Hog Heaven Sports Bar/ Jan 2014 to Mar 2019

- Performed in an extremely fast paced famous tourist as well as local driven bar.
- Worked closely management at all times to continue a consistent, yet still cutting edge flow to keep up with trends as well as hold on to tradition.
- Processed \$2500 in daily revenue on average day with totals as high as \$5000 during special events and promotions.

Key Largo, FL

Ocean Reef Club/ Jan 2011 to Jan 2014

- Server and bartender at an elite private club, resort and marina.
- Responsible for vast menu and ingredient knowledge and wine pairing.
- Trained to anticipate needs in advance and equipped with the ability to guide members through and amazing dining experience from start to finish.

Portland, ME

Dimillo's Floating Restaurant/Jan 2003 to Jan 2008

- Server and bartender to a well-known, high volume, quality seasonal restaurant and marina
- Responsible for catering to large amounts of high profile, important private functions and events.

Bartender

St John, USVI

The Balcony/Jan 2007 to Jun 2007

- Bartender, server and management at a fantastic island tourist destination.
- Responsible for making unforgettable memories for patrons on a daily basis as well as
 exotic drink knowledge and fast paced service consistently delivered with a friendly
 attitude.

Assistant General Manager

Kittery, ME

Weathervane Seafood Restaurants/ May 2000 to Jan 2004

- Coordinated monthly budgets, managed profit and loss and consistently met desired margin targets for my store as well as others in need within the chain.
- Motivated and led team members to work together to achieve targets.
- Increased annual profit by streamlining processes and improving staff knowledge of optimal procedures. Corporate trainer.
- Developed employee handbook, detailed job descriptions and workflow plans to formalize operational systems and procedures.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Brewer High School 1996

Brewer, ME

Graduated co-valedictorian of the class of 1996. General studies and math.

Certificate: Web Development, Software Engineering

Worcester State University Jan 2020

Worcester, MA

WEBSITES, PORTFOLIOS, PROFILES

- https://www.linkedin.com/in/carrye-gaulin-5662b21b7/
- https://github.com/carryegaulin31